NICK BOYSKO

SKILLS AND QUALIFICATIONS



Complex Problem-Solving
Software Development
Software Improvements
Program Coding
Quality Assurance
Computer Engineering

RELEVANT COURSEWORK



Software I Software II Foundations I

PERSONAL PROJECTS



Sample personal projects can be viewed using the following link: https://github.com/nickboysko?tab=repositories

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

OSU Blockchain Club Intramural Basketball SAE Fraternity (Pledge Class Fall 2023)

CONTACT



(614) 956-8808 Boysko.1@buckeyemail.osu.edu https://www.linkedin.com/in/nickboysko/



PROFILE

Highly motivated and hardworking computer science student with knowledge of application development, configuration management, and database design. Strong work ethic and active listening skills developed through twelve years in competitive sports. Utilize excellent problem-solving skills to take the initiative and seek out new challenges. Eager to apply my academic knowledge to a hands-on summer internship in a technology role.



EXPERIENCE

BASKETBALL REFEREE – Various Organizations May 2023 to Present

- Worked well under pressure during games.
- Demonstrated effective conflict resolution skills.
- Exhibited strong leadership and communication skills to navigate players, coaches and parents.

GOLF COURSE ASSISTANT – Wedgewood Golf and Fitness March 2022 to August 2023

- Maintained inventories of equipment.
- Ensured equipment was cleaned and stored properly.
- Retrieved items for members when requested.
- Utilized effective communication skills to respond to inquiries from members regarding service offerings.
- Demonstrated proficiency in safely operating power equipment such as golf carts, flatbeds and utility vehicles.

SANDWICH ARTIST – Subway May 2021 to May 2022

- Balanced receipts and payments in cash registers.
- Organized dining, service, and kitchen areas.
- Demonstrated ability to work collaboratively with diverse teams and customers.
- Trained three new employees in proper food safety procedures and sanitation regulations.
- Communicated with customers regarding orders, comments, and complaints.



EDUCATION

Computer Science Candidate The Ohio State University, Columbus, Ohio Current Cumulative GPA 3.6

Graduated from Olentangy High School Powell, Ohio GPA